Suresh Ch



sureshch0963@gmail.com



8555058584



linkedin.com/in/ch-suresh-47a625197



https://sureshch97.github.io/myportfolio/

Summary

Developed Product Features from scratch using MERN Stack (MongoDB, Express, React). Skilled in JavaScript, python, React, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and MongoDB.

Specialized in Computer Science Engineering from (VITAE) Vignan Institute Of Technology and Aeronautical Engineering

Experience



Full Stack Engineer

Yours, Mentor

Dec 2020 - Present (8 months +)

Full Stack Engineer Yours mentor Dec 2020 - Present - Trained in Full Stack Product Development with Yours Mentor company.

-I also developed Projects Using React.js , Node.js and Java Script

Education



Vignan's Institute of Technology & Aeronautical Engineering

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science

2016 - 2020

- -Scored 6.89 CGPA Overall in B.Tech
- -Participated in Ethical Hacking Contest

Nagarjuna junior college

Intermediate, M.P.C

2014 - 2016

-Scored 95% Overall in Intermediate

Zilla Parishad High School

S.S.C

2013 - 2014

- -Scored 8.5 CGPA in acadamics
- -got medals in Sports and Essay writing competion in Independence day celebrations

Licenses & Certifications



AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials - Amazon Web Services (AWS)



python(Basic) - HackerRank

- MERN Stack Front To Back: Full Stack React, Redux & Node.js Udemy UC-ececeb71-d55b-4c48-ac0e-f2d9b43b4d17
- Programming Foundations: Web Security LinkedIn Learning · Course Certificate Ab3fTfLp07dV1C-ejwttr0J5Wvih
- Modern java Script From The Beginning Udemy UC-e22fdd84-dcbe-474b-aada-f74e9a7d982d
- **ETHICAL HACKING** ROBOSAPIENS TECHNOLOGIES Pvt. Ltd.
- complete java MANAC INFOTECH PRIVATE LIMITED ELT/20190957

Skills

JavaScript • React.js • Node.js • MongoDB • Express.js • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Bootstrap • Git